New York State Tenants and Neighbors, Inc; Records apap198
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative, 1973-2000, Undated; 3; 9.8 cubic ft.
  - Information on Landlord Violations Including Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Legislation Housing Trust Fund, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - Summary of 1985 Legislation (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - 1985 Legislature Last Weeks of Session (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 17-18)
  - Testimony of Assemblyman Pete Grannis Board of Estimate Hearing, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Legislation, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 20-23)
  - A. 8107, A. 5576 Tenants and Not for Profit Organizations That Provide Housing, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - Omnibus Housing Bill Extension of Rent Laws, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - California Legislature, 1985 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - Governor's Program Bill, 1985 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - Rules of the Senate, 1985-1986 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 3)
  - Protection to Tenants in Rental Buildings Subject to Conversion to Cooperatives and Condominiums Bill, 1985 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Major Capital Improvements Memorandums, Bill Jackets, DHCR, 1985 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Housing Production with City Funds for Low and Moderate Income Families, 1985-1986 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - J-51 Real Property Tax Law Bill and Memorandum, 1985-1986 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Legislative Commission Expenditure Review Memorandum Report to the Legislature, 1986 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - NYS Assembly Correspondence, 1986 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - The Tax Law, 1986 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 10)
  - Reverse Mortgages, 1986-1990 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - Court Merger Bill, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - J-51 Reform Coalition, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - "Bona Fide" Tenants State Assembly Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Legislation Omnibus Bill, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - J-51 Reform Coalition and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - New York State Tax Reform and Reduction Act of 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - Tax Reform, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Private Housing Finance Law, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Gay Life Partners Supreme Court Appelate Division, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - Personal Use Evictions Legislation, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Legislation Including Bill Jackets and Descriptive Information Regarding Omnibus Bill, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 23)
  - Concept of Unconscionability and Related Bill Jackets, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - Bill Jackets, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - Federal Pre-payment Registration, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 26)
  - Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 27)
  - Attorney General Program Bill to Sponsor Duty to Cure Violations, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 28)
  - A. 8972, A. 3054, A. 4953, A. 6795, A. 2726 Bill Jackets, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 29)
  - Coalition to Reform MCI, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 30)
  - In Rem Early Warning Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 31)
  - Rules of the Senate/ Rules of the Assembly, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 32)
  - Warehousing Campaign, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 33)
  - Governor's Program Bills and Related Information, 1987-1989 (Box 5 (3-Legislative), Folder 34-35)
  - New York City Rent Extenders, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - State Senator Election Campaign, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - Legislation, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 3)
  - Major Capital Improvements Workshop Sponsored by NYSTNC, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Anti-Warehousing Campaign, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Anti-Warehousing Legislation and Materials on NYSTNC's Anti-Warehousing Commission, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Bill Jackets for Legislature Reforms, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Bill Jackets and Legislative Memorandums, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 9-10)
  - Senior Citizen Rent Increase Exemption (SCRIE), 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Memorandums on Vocate and Repair Issues, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - Fair Share Housing Act A. 5064, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - New York City Council Intro 1329, Intro 1213, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - DHCR on Major Capital Improvements (MCI), 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - Private Housing Finance Law, Chapter 252, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - Primary Residents Bill Jackets and Memorandums, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - Bill Jackets, Memorandums and Related Newsclippings, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 18-19)
  - Assorted NYS Assembly and Cambridge, Massachusetts Materials, 1989; 1990 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - Coalition to Reform MCI, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Rules of the Senate, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 22)
  - New York State Attorney General Program Bills, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 23)
  - Major Capital Improvements (MCI), 1989-1992 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - Property Tax Assessment, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - Legislation, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - Legislation and Memorandum in Support for MCI Reform, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - Govenor's Program Bill Memorandum, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 3)
  - Queens, 1990-1992 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Attorney General Program Bills Addressed to Michael McKee, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 5-6)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Govenor's Program Bill A. 7594, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - Bawdy House Bill, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - Warranty of Habitability and Other Legislation, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 10-11)
  - Warranty of Habitability Legislative Memorandums, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - DHRC Rent Administration and Rent Reform Bill, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - Warranty of Habitability Weakener Veto, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - DHCR Rent Administration Reform and Equity Act, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - Major Capital Improvements (MCI), 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - Legislation Including Testimony Before the Housing and Buildings Committee of NYC Council, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (CHAS), 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Legislation, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 19-20)
  - Legislation Including Memorandums for Mayor's Office, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Loans and Co-Op Conversions Including Bill Jackets, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 23)
  - Govenor Mario Cuomo's "Message to the Legislature" Report, 1992 January 8 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - Luxury Decontrol Testimony, 1992 March 25 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - Joint Public Hearing on the Federal Housing Oppurtunity for People Everywhere (HOPE) Program, 1992 July 16 (Box 7 (3-Legislative), Folder 26)
  - Legislation, 1992 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 1-3)
  - Fundraising for Members of Legislature, 1992 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1992 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - State Senator Dean Skelos, 1992 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (CHAS), 1992-1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Invitations to Political Events and Fundraisers, 1992-1996 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - S. 5163 Legislative Memorandum, 1993 June 8 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - New York State Senate Rent Regulations Report, 1993 June 10 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 10)
  - Vacancy Decontrol S. 3424-A Legislative Memorandum, 1993 June 14 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - S. 4898-A, S. 4898-B Legislative Memorandums, 1993 June 21; 1993 June 28 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - S. 6177 Legislative Memorandum, 1993 July 5 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - A. 8859 Act to Ammend Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1993 July 6 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill Jackets 4900A and 4900B, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - Legislation Extender, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - S. 3423 Conversion of Rental Residental Property to Cooperative or Condominium, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - Congressional Hearing on Co-Op Financing, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Extender Includes Advisory Memorandums on Rent Registration and Rent Increase, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Legislative Memorandums in Opposition Sponsored by Either Senator Bruno or Senator Hannon, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Legislation to Extend the Laws of 1973, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 22)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 23)
  - Rent Law Campaign, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - Rent Extender Bill, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - Bill Jackets, 1993 (Box 8 (3-Legislative), Folder 26)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 1-3)
  - Legislation Including Memorandums, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Real Property Tax Report Commission, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Govenor's Program Bill, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Extension of Emergency Rent Stabilization, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Legislation to Extend Emergency Tenant Protection Laws of 1974, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 8-9)
  - Senator Maltese, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 10)
  - Senator John Marchi, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - Rent Regulation, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - NYS Senate Public Hearing on Rent Regulation, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - Extension of Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Legislation for Rent Extender Bill, 1993 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - Mitchell-Lama Residents Coalition Includes Legislative Bill, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - New York State Senator Padavan, 1993-1997 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - Bill Jackets on Major Capital Improvements and Related Legislative Materials, 1994 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Gubanetorial Campaign Cuomo versus Pataki, 1994 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Vacancy Allowance, 1994 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - Research on Landlords, 1995 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Preliminary Legislative Wrap-Up Report, 1995 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 22)
  - Shared Meters, Chapter 186, 1995 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 23)
  - Legislation, 1995-1996 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - New York State Board of Elections Disclosure Statement, 1996 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - A. 10927-A Materials and Related Correspondence with Michael McKee, 1996; 1997 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 26)
  - New York City Tax Lien and Distressed Buildings, 1996 April 19 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 27)
  - State Senator Sampson, 1997 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 28)
  - Extenders to ETPA, 1997 (Box 9 (3-Legislative), Folder 29)
  - Bill to Amend the Real Property Actions and Proceedings Law, 1997 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1997 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - A. 868 Amendment of Real Property Actions Proceedings Law, 1997 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 3)
  - Rent Law Presentations, 1997 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Intro 994A, 1997 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 5-6)
  - Rent Campaign, 1997 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 7-8)
  - Assembly Record of Proceedings, 1997 March 17 (Box 10 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - The Rent Regulation Reform Act Chapter 116, 1997 (Box 11 (3-Legislative), Folder 1-3)
  - State Senator Maltese, 1997 (Box 11 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Legislation, 1998 (Box 11 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Maximum Base Rent, 1999 (Box 11 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Assorted NYS Assembly and Senate Supportive Materials, Undated (Box 11 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
- Tenant Organizations & Campaigns, 1973-2000, Undated; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  The Tenant Organizations & Campaigns series is arranged chronologically.
  The Tenant Organizations and Campaigns series focuses on tenant organizations outside of New York State, however some New York State campaigns are also kept in this series. Smaller renter rights organizations are also represented here.
  - Various Organizations, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Out of State Tenant Organizations, 1974-1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Home Front, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Fresh Meadows Tenants Association Newsletters, 1975-1982 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - Columbia Tenants Union, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - Interlaken Residents Association, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - Tenants Union of the West Side, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - Tudor City Association and Mid Manhattan Neighborhood Association, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Westchester Tenants Union, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 9)
  - Pratt Institute Center For Community And Environmental Development, 1977 September (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 10)
  - California Housing Action Information Network, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 11)
  - Park West Village Tenants Association, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 12)
  - Tenants United, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 13)
  - Coalition Against Rent Increase Pass-Alongs, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 14)
  - Tarrytown Tenants Association, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 15)
  - The Planners Network, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 16)
  - Citizens Alliance, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 17)
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 18)
  - City Limits, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 19)
  - Co-Op City Council, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 20)
  - Temporary State Commission on Rental Housing Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 21)
  - Temporary State Commission on Mental Housing Public Hearing Notes, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 23)
  - Shepherd House Tenants, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 24)
  - Temporary State Commission on Rental Housing, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 25-27)
  - United Tenants of Albany Rent Control, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 28)
  - New York City Administrative Code, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 29)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing, 1978-1997 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 30)
  - Temporary State Commission on Rental Housing, 1979 February 27 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 31)
  - Temporary State Commission on Rental Housing Handicap Rent Increase Exemption, 1979 February 28 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 32)
  - Temporary State Commission On Rental Housing, 1979 August 12 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 33)
  - Columbia Tenants Union, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 34)
  - Community Housing Involvement Program, Inc., 1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 35)
  - Temporary State Commission on Rental Housing, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 36-37)
  - Temporary State Commission on Rental Housing Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 38)
  - Project Research, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 39)
  - Coalition Against Redlining Federal Reserve Board Hearing, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 40)
  - Greystone/Freedom of Information Law, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 41)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Companies, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 42)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Companies Program, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 43)
  - New York State Temporary Commission on Lobbying, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 44)
  - Rural Preservation Companies, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Statutory Rights of Tenants, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Code Enforcement, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing, 1981-1993 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - New York State Rural Housing Advocates, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - Citizens Unity Board, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - Coalition of Tenants of Non-Profit Institutional Landlords, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Los Sures Southside United Housing, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 9)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 10)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 11)
  - Small Business Task Force, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 12)
  - Small Building Task Force, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 13)
  - St. Nicholas Neighborhood Preservation and Housing Rehabilitation Corporation, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 14)
  - Various Tenant Organizations, 1983 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 15)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Companies Funding Issues, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 16-17)
  - Cambridge, MA Tenant and Rent Issues, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 18)
  - Various Tenant Organizations, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 19)
  - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, Inc. (NYC), 1983-1990 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 20)
  - Catholic Charities/Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of New York, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 21)
  - Small Building Owners Assocation, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 22)
  - West Tenants Union Co-Op Conversion Material, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 23)
  - Small Property Owners of New York, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 24)
  - Bank Powers, 1984-1987 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 25)
  - Apartment House Institute, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 26)
  - Housing Justice Campaign, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 27)
  - Price Index Campaign, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 28)
  - Tenant Protection Campaign, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 29-31)
  - Tenant Protection Campaign Strategic Issues, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 32)
  - 421-A Tenants Coalition, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 33)
  - Price Index, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 34)
  - January 1987 Rent Stabilization Code Background Information, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 35)
  - Housing Justice Campaign, 1985-1990 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 36)
  - Glen Oaks Tenant Association, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 37)
  - New York State Temporary Commission on Lobbying, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 38)
  - SRO Tenants Rights Coalition, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Lobby Registration, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Bank Powers Community Service Society, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1988-1993 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - Community Action for Legal Support Services, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - Mayor Dinkins Administration Tenant Unity Coalition, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - Non-Profit Resource Center, Inc. The 1990 Agenda (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Stuyvesant Town Tenants Association, 1990-1993 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 9)
  - Eastern Paralyzed Veterans Association, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 10)
  - The City Project, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 11)
  - Queens League of United Tenants, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 12)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1992-1994 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 13)
  - Canadian Tenant Housing, 1992-1996 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 14)
  - Pride Agenda, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 15)
  - United Tenants of Albany 20th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 16)
  - Westchester Tenants League, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 17)
  - Rent Regulation - Various Tenant Organizations, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 18)
  - Political Action Committee, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 19)
  - Long Beach, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 20-21)
  - Long Beach Herald, Tribune, and Independent Voice, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 22-23)
  - Supreme Court of the State Of New York: Walton v. City of Long Beach, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 24)
  - 19 East 80th street Tenants Association, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 25)
  - Leo House, 1996-1998 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 26)
  - Rent Law Campaign Committee, 1997 July 31 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 27)
  - Administrative Campaign, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 28-30)
  - Campaign and McKee Material, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Tenant Organizations & Campaigns), Folder 31)